[Music]
Biryani,
oh biryani, next to it is
sambar, oh
machi machi, taste this a little,
machi machi machi, machi machi.  Eat a little
.
Hey, don't put a knife in the middle
.  Smell it a little and sing.
Hey, just come to my nose, eat it, and
watch it.
You don't know if I'm fasting.
You just showed it.   If there
was something wrong.  Oh Allah, what did
you
forget to do for me, even though I know I will be fasting during Ramadan?
[Music]
Eat, eat   It's only been
two days, so there's still 28 days left,
so let's see.   It's been
eight days, there are still 22 days left.   It's been
12 days, there's still 18 days, it's already
20 days, there's still 10 days, let
's eat
[music] If there's only
one more day, what if there's nothing else, then go and
see what happens next.
[Music]
Ezhugu Gundula Vada Govinda Govinda, is this a
museum or a temple of Perumal?
I too will be found in a field beyond Perumal
.  This is enough for the month of Purattasi
.  Swami Theertham family,
Swami Tozhasi family, Swami Kumkumam
family, all come to mind and
are said to be three fold.  Look, Chanda Bhai, you have no fear
.  Any five people can come and
spend Rs. 100 and buy half a kilo of rice in the evening and
feed their family.
What will happen if this continues?
Lord, please look at Satan.
What if Madhavan is gone? What do I have to do?
Govinda watched.
[Music]
Don't just stand there for months.   Have
darshan of the Lord and then go
.  Just stay away.
Just buy it before going for darshan.
500 Sami, don't take a selfie, I
want to take a selfie. 000 Oh, 000 Take the reels,
take the reels,
Sami, evening,
hey, 150 Ma, Kekkuda, I don't want anything, Vibhuti, come, enter, go, stay,
you are not hunting, I just came, don't put anything in it, Sami, I'm not
coming to some temple,
go, business will come and disturb you, don't put
money in it,
dad, the bus will come in five minutes.  I'll
pick you up and call you. Wait,
okay, brother, brother,
you can come too.
I have work tomorrow,
otherwise I won't come.
I'm alone, I can't
go with him, why don't you take a bus and
send me to Tirupati? I'm also with
you, what will you do if I get lost?
Hey, you won't be able to get away, that's why I'm
booking you a ticket on the Zink bus
.  Is it zinc?  In that case,
I often travel by Zink bus
.  It also has a live tracking
option.  Where are you?  Where have you gone
?  I
will watch everything from here.  There
are experienced marshals here.
We don't need to be afraid.  Not only that,
it also has comfortable seating, a
safe ride, and 24/7 customer support
.  The main thing is that there are toilet facilities
.  Do you also want to travel with a 15% discount like my brother
?
Use the coupon code shown on the screen.  If you
want more details, click on the link in the description and check it out
.
Come and see the bus.  Okay, I'll go.
Hey, live talk, our father is a
sex addict.  Okay,
I'll go
What are you doing?   Let's
buy all the chicken and mutton,
come home, and give this scoundrel a good bath
.
Bro,
would you like a chicken piece?
Oh my God, I'm fasting, bro.
Chicken
or mutton is a fast, sir.  We do
n't have this crazy Greta Slam, bro.   It's just a
matter of digging and digging.  There's a price to pay for all that,
bro.  Bro, you
don't want to be loud, bro, you don't want to be serious, bro.
Great, great, if you can control this, it's a
big deal.  Super.
[Music]
Control
What control?  Now this guy is
going to take control.  If he's the one eating chicken pieces,
I'm screwed.  If you bought a piece and
ate it, why
don't you eat sambar when you come back? You crazy boy, you crazy boy, oh, you're going to die.
Put sambar sauce on it,
oh, oh, a
whole chicken, a whole chicken, look there,
look there, look there, if
you want, would you try just one piece?
Say what you want, say what you want,
say what you want.   Just
buy one piece.   Don't feel
like we're buying it, bro.   It's
bad until he says he'll give it to me.
This control is what takes you somewhere, and when you're not sure,
this confident guy wo
n't eat this or that.
I'm going to the Sambar Idli
Pattu stall this month.
Tell me, bro.   If you don't
mind, he's changed his mind.
[Music]
Listen to that chicken piece, listen to that chicken piece.
[Applause] Can you give me
some of that water bottle?
Control Control
[Music]
Come on, you too, have your Paratasia
biscuits
. I don't want eggs mixed in the biscuits.  The egg started to turn, it started to turn, I
can't bear this trouble
[Music] I've been
tempted for a month, can you control it?
[Music]
Brother, is there any non-veg hotel near here? [Music
]
Are you watching the match in the shot? What's
the score?
Chicken 65
Rohit, egg,
egg,
hello,
brother, my birthday treat has arrived at the market.
[Music]
Ah, I've been suffering for three months, and the
pleasure of eating by myself is unique.
Thank you for the delicious biryani.
What, have you started yet?
The taste of Machi Biryani is amazing.   I
bought it myself, because it was a very crowded place.  I'm really
hungry, son.
Today's top news: There was a
lizard in the biryani at Dennis Hotel, causing
a stir.  Five people died.   If
someone in the hotel
thinks that we are the only ones who can afford a hotel like this in this town, we are in the same situation.
What do you mean, you're in
shock?
[Music]